DEVDEEP BANERJEE

Unreal Developer

+91 9916267332

•

devdeep01@gmail.com



/devdeep-banerjee



github.com/devdeep14



PROFILE

Passionate game maker, completed Master's degree in Game Technology from ICAT Bangalore. Having 4+ years of working experience as a digital designer in web design and development. Seeking an opportunity to enter the gaming industry as Unreal Developer, having proficient knowledge in Game Development tool Unreal game engines with strong understanding of blueprint scripting, materials & shaders, maths 3D, programming and graphics libraries.

GAME ENGINE SKILLS

devdeep14.github.io/devportfolio

- UNREAL ENGINE Good understanding of Unreal GUI, asset bundles, blueprint scripting
- MATERIALS Strong knowledge of node based material shader language
- 3D MATH Strong base in linear algebra and vector math
- CODING Good Understanding of C and C++ programming languages
- GRAPHICS LIBRARY Understanding of industry standard graphics library

EDUCATION

MASTERS IN GAME TECHNOLOGY (MSc)

ICAT Design & Media College 2021 - 2023 Completing my masters in game technology from ICAT design & media college, affiliated to Alaqappa University

Learnt the basics of game design challenges & development process along with game engines such as Unity & Unreal with understanding of materials/shaders.

For final year project, designed an action-adventure FPS game with agent based missions in mountain valley of India

BACHELORS IN COMPUTER APPLICATION (BCA)

Bangalore University 2013 - 2016 Completed my graduation in computer science from City College - Jayanagar, affiliated to Bangalore University

For final year project, created fully-functional insurance website which consists of purchase, claim & renew policy sections to manage user's account details

WORK EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL DESIGNER

Element14 Sept, 2019 - Sept, 2021 Part of Global Creative Services team, designing & developing complete marketing campaigns for element14 Asia-Pacific and clients based in Farnell EU & Newark NA

Creating form integrated landing pages & designing homepage leaderboard, supplier funded banners / product slots and merchandising eSpot banners

Brand reviewed marketing campaigns deployed across 42 sites in 26 languages, also worked in Adobe Target A/B testing for analyzing campaign results

WEB DESIGNER

CRMIT Solutions July, 2017 - July, 2019 Designing, developing & maintaining company website along with creating marketing emailer campaigns and product landing pages.

Creating visual imagery for company branding, creating corporate brochures, whitepapers, infographics and marketing slides

COURSES

• UNREAL ENGINE 5 C++ DEVELOPER

GameDev.tv Team - Udemy 2022 - 2023

SKILLS

- C and C++
- Unreal Game Engine
- Maya and Zbrush
- Substance 3D
- HTML-CSS
- Bootstrap
- Photoshop / Illustrator
- Adobe XD / Figma

KEY INTERESTS

- Game Concept & Ideation
- Game Design & Visualization
- Visual Motion Graphics

SOFT SKILLS

- Critical-thinking
- Good communication
- Problem solving abilities

HOBBIES











